John Dildine and Ginny Dildine papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 5: Photographic materials
  - Sara Grey, undated, 1 photograph: black and white; 7 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH270 (Box 7)
    Photo of Grey playing guitar, in performance.
  - Carol Hedin and Alan Damron, circa 1960s, 1 photograph: black and white; 10 in. x 8 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH271 (Box 7)
    Studio portrait credited to Randy Silver.
  - Carol Hedin, Donal Leace, and an unidentified person, undated, 1 photograph: black and white; 4 in. x 4 1/2 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH272 (Box 7)
  - Frank Proffitt, undated, 1 photograph: black and white; 10 in. x 7 3/4 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH273 (Box 7)
  - Mike Seeger, Hedy West, and two other people, undated, 1 photograph: black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 8 1/4 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH274 (Box 7)
    Hedy West (in sunglasses), Mike Seeger (far right), photographed at an outdoor event.
  - Pete Seeger, undated, 1 photograph: black and white; 10 in. x 8 in.; AFC 2018/009: PH275 (Box 7)
- Series 6: Drawings, approx. 20 black-and-white prints
  - Drawings for puppets, undated, 12 in. x 9 in. or smaller; AFC 2018/009: GR01-GR36 (Box 8)
    Drawings and instructions created by Ginny Dildine. The original arrangement of items has been retained.
- Series 7: Posters
  - Mariposa Folk Festival poster, 1972, 1 poster: color; 25 in. x 18 1/4 in.; AFC 2018/009: GR35 (Oversize folder 1)
    A poster for the folk festival, in indigo and white.
  - National Park Service Christmas holiday event poster, undated, 1 poster (rigid): color; 17 in. x 14 in.; AFC 2018/009: GR36 (Oversize folder 1)
    A National Park Service poster to publicize Christmas holiday programs. The Dildine Family's "Christmas Puppet Show" is a featured event.
  - Dildine marionettes, undated, 1 poster: black and white; 8 in. x 17 in.; AFC 2018/009: GR37 (Oversize folder 1)
    A printed poster from a hand-drawn source. The performance was given at Orange County Community College.
  - The Dildine Family Folk Songs and Marionettes, undated, 1 poster: black and white; 17 in. x 11 in.; AFC 2018/009: GR38 (Oversize folder 1)
    A printed poster from a hand-drawn source. The event location is not identified, but may be the same as for AFC 2018/009: GR37. The illustration features a frog playing a banjo.
- Series 8: Artifacts
  59 items (including the binder and its contents).
  - The Dildine Family: Folksongs with Visuals, circa 1970s (Box 9)
    The original three-ring notebook in which the manuscript materials in boxes-folders 2/4 to 2/8 were housed.
  - Badges from various events and festivals, circa 1960s-1990s (Boxes 10-11)
    Items include metal-backed buttons and cloth patches, as well as ribbons and paper ID badges.